hi this is PR Sund welcome to pre-market
report sponsored by tax.com and Finn
bingo.com
yesterday the market recovered it was a
fantastic recovery but look at the
market last Tuesday I'm not talking
about yesterday the last Tuesday the
Nifty future low was
177,000 in the next 2 to 3 days from
17,000 it has gone up to
17,500 plus I think
17515 is the
high then came a severe selling just in
two trading session from
17,500 plus to around
16,900 just next one trading session
from 169 to
173 so if you see it is a total swing of
more than 1,500 point in just matter of
one week 1,500 in Nifty if you look at
the bank Nifty it can be 3,000 to 4,000
Point swing in just
one
week so one thing for sure the markets
are hugely
volatile and today is Wednesday don't
forget every Wednesday also markets tend
to
be more
volatile and to add fuel to the fire and
today we have RBA policy around 10:
a.m. but
however from the market perspective RB
event should be a
nonevent one thing is that the inflation
is in the comfortable Zone RBI Target
for inflation is 4% plus or minus
2% that means 2% to 6% RBA is
comfortable with the inflation and our
inflation was around 4.8% so which is
well within the
range and second thing though GDP data
was good but this new wave of Corona the
Omicron
brings some kind of uncertainty to the
near future so therefore RBI may be
willing to wait and watch before
increasing the interest
rate just like in us what they did the
before actually increasing or before
actually doing the tapping of the bond
purchases so they prepared the market
few months ahead of the time so RBA may
start preparing the market for future
hike so that process may
start some analyst said reverse report
rate may be hiked and some say no
there'll be no change and whether they
change or not so that is actually
immaterial for the stock
market so we have only one big concern
now is the FIA
selling whether the market trade at
17,500 or whether the market trade at
16,900
or whether Market trade around
17,300 they just don't care they just
keep
selling and yesterday such a powerful
short covering and Nifty shot up more
than 300 point and Bank Nifty more than
th000 Point still at the end of the day
we have seen F selling more than 2,500
CR so one thing is that you know the
market drifted down from 175 to below 17
uh for two reasons one is the Omicron
case and that is subsiding all over the
world and no severe uh illness or no
death has been reported so far and
second one is this uh us jobs data
induced uh sell off in
NASDAQ NASDAQ fell 2% on Friday but on
Monday and Tuesday uh it has shot up
nearly uh 4 % so more than double of
what they have
lost and many media have been saying
that you know so this Friday there's an
inflation data in us so they say
inflation data is going to be very very
bad so that's going to be highest in the
past
decades but however I defer you know
because I quoted even the last time when
the inflation came highest multi- decade
High I just quoted you know so
inflation data is a lag indicator just
because the Baltic dry index which was
more than double in the month of October
so that is why in the month of November
the inflation data was very high but in
the month of November the Baltic dry
index has fallen more than
50% so which means approximately in a
Layman point of view the Fright
charges uh in shipping uh has come down
by more than 50% in the month of
November so there is no reason for
multi- decade High inflation in the
month of
December so anyway uh smart money can
understand all these things so that's
why smart money have used the dip as an
opportunity in US market to buy the
shares so anyway Facebook was down 20%
and you know F stocks or F Plus stocks
were down by 10% so that's the right
time for entering for the longterm
investors and that is what I've also
been saying here also don't believe in
all kinds of theories you know uh people
are moving money from India to China if
they're moving to China then the Chinese
market should do well right and Chinese
markets you know has been in trouble for
many many years not one year or not two
year but nearly 13 14
years and you know also the sebi data
shows the money you know it is true that
f are selling uh probably they are
selling
to just uh teach a lesson to
somebody uh but they are not actually
moving the money out of
India so if they're moving the money out
of India then you know it should reflect
in uh rupee movement so rupee is still
trading around
7550 You know despite f are selling
85,000 crores in just in a of 2 and a
half
months so well they're all big stories
okay uh today uh is z Nifty indicating a
opening above yesterday's high so
technically uh that is a big positive
those who have shed yesterday in the
last half an hour so they may have to
run for cover and uh once again
yesterday my prediction has gone
terribly wrong I thought 17,100 will be
the resistance
but actually the resistance came at
17,300 so during this High volatile you
know tgof war between FIA and domestic
institutions you know it's not even a
tgof war it's just a
war and you know this kind of times you
know markets tend to move very very
violently so there is no point in
predicting the market in the morning so
we have to react as and when the market
moves uh during the market hours
so therefore I refrain from predicting
the market move so although I'm thinking
you know uh once again 17,100 to be the
support and of course because fa is
continuously selling so if the markets
move significantly higher maybe towards
17,400 and once again they will start
selling so only good thing is that you
know after one or two days of Gap now
domestic institutions are
buying more than what f are selling so
that may support so uh FAS are all out
to bring down the markets the diis are
all out to support the market so during
this war and the markets tend to move
very very violently and making trading
very very difficult so once again expect
a high volatile market so don't be happy
with The Gap up so so will not be
surprised if some FAS puts a sell order
at
9:15 yeah so let us see how the market
goes the stock specific you know so I
I've given some Clues yesterday but I
still favor uh selling ,000 rupees put
option in tata still and yesterday
Metals index has outperformed very well
and I think it will continue going
forward so hope you enjoyed watching the
video thank you for watching